feng-gui.com 2017-06-08

# Feng-GUI - Privacy Policy | Effective Visuals

## Feng-GUI Privacy Policy

_Last modified: August 1, 2010_

At Feng-GUI we recognise that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Feng-GUI Inc. or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies; collectively, Feng-GUI's "services". In addition, where more detailed information is needed to explain our privacy practices, we post supplementary privacy notices to describe how particular services process personal information.(referred as "Personal Information" in this document).

### Information that we collect and how we use it

We offer a number of services that do not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us, such as Feng-GUI free Attention Heatmap. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information: 

**Information you provide** \- When you sign up for a Feng-GUI Account or another Feng-GUI service or promotion that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). For certain services, we may also request credit card or other payment account information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. We may combine the information that you submit under your account with information from other Feng-GUI services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information. 

**Cookies** \- When you visit Feng-GUI, we may send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters that uniquely identifies your browser - to your computer. We use cookies to improve the quality of our services. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent so that you can decide whether or not to accept any cookies on a case-by-case basis.

**Log information** \- When you access Feng-GUI services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

**User communications** \- When you send email or other communications to Feng-GUI, we may retain those communications in order to process your enquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

**Affiliated sites** \- We offer some of our services in connection with other websites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to Feng-GUI in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. 

Feng-GUI only processes personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and/or the supplementary privacy notices for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include: 

* Providing our services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising; 

* Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services; 

* Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; and 

* Developing new services. 

You can find more information about how we process personal information by referring to the supplementary privacy notices for particular services. 

Feng-GUI processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. We may process personal information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our partners. 

### Choices for personal information

When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask that you provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different from the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. 

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the specific service privacy notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the supplementary service privacy notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Feng-GUI features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case Feng-GUI may not be able to provide those services to you. 

### Information sharing

Feng-GUI only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Feng-GUI in the following limited circumstances: 

* We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information. 

* We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

* We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Feng-GUI, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. 

If Feng-GUI becomes involved in a merger, acquisition or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregate non-personal information, this is information that is recorded about users and collected into groups so that it no longer reflects or references an individually identifiable user. Such information does not identify you individually. 

### Information security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

We restrict access to personal information to Feng-GUI employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

### Data integrity

Feng-GUI processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to make sure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to make sure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

### Accessing and updating personal information

When you use Feng-GUI services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes.   
We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes) or for which access is not otherwise required.   
In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Some of our services have different procedures to access, correct or delete users' personal information. We provide the details for these procedures in the specific privacy notices or FAQs for these services. 

### Enforcement

Feng-GUI regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or Feng-GUI's treatment of personal information by emailing us at info feng-gui.com  
When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is Feng-GUI's policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Feng-GUI and an individual. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent and we expect that most changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes).   
If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at any time by emailing info feng-gui.com
